A Guide to the Population Council records, Central Files, Accession 2, RG 2, Series 1 to Series 4 FA432
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Accession 2, Central Files, 1957-1983; bulk; 2; 286 Cubic Feet
  - Administration File, 3; 110.4 Cubic Feet Boxes 204-479.
    - Berelson, Bernard - Correspondence - Mott, Stewart Rawlings (Box 260, Folder 2402)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Correspondence - Mc (Box 260, Folder 2403)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Correspondence - Mc, 1963-1966 (Box 260, Folder 2404)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Correspondence - McGranahan, Donald V., 1974-1975 (Box 260, Folder 2405)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Correspondence - McGranahan, Donald V., 1964 (Box 260, Folder 2406)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Correspondence - McPhee, William, 1963-1965 (Box 260, Folder 2407)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Correspondence - N, 1962-1976 (Box 260, Folder 2408)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Correspondence - O, 1963-1975 (Box 260, Folder 2409)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Correspondence - P-Q, 1962-1975 (Box 260, Folder 2410)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Correspondence - Page, Tanya (Box 261, Folder 2411)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Correspondence - Perkin, Gordon, 1969-1971 (Box 261, Folder 2412)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Correspondence - Phatak, Leela, 1973-1974 (Box 261, Folder 2413)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Correspondence - Povey, George, 1971-1972 (Box 261, Folder 2414)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Correspondence - Pradervand, Pierre, 1970-1974 (Box 261, Folder 2415)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Correspondence - R (Box 261, Folder 2416)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Correspondence - R, 1961-1966 (Box 261, Folder 2417)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Correspondence - Ruder and Finn (Box 261, Folder 2418)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Correspondence - Ryder, Norman B., 1969-1973 (Box 261, Folder 2419)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Correspondence - S (Box 261, Folder 2420)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Correspondence - S (Box 261, Folder 2421)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Correspondence - Schramm, Wilbur (Box 261, Folder 2422)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Correspondence - Sills, D.L. (Box 261, Folder 2423)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Correspondence - Singer, S. Fred, 1969-1973 (Box 261, Folder 2424)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Correspondence - T (Box 262, Folder 2425)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Correspondence - T (Box 262, Folder 2426)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Correspondence - Talbot, Nathan, 1975-1976 (Box 262, Folder 2427)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Correspondence - U-V, 1975 (Box 262, Folder 2428)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Correspondence - V, 1962-1963 (Box 262, Folder 2429)
    - Berelson, Bernard Correspondence - Valentei, Dimitri, 1970-1974 (Box 262, Folder 2430)
    - Berelson, Bernard Correspondence - W, 1974-1976 (Box 262, Folder 2431)
    - Berelson, Bernard Correspondence - W (Box 262, Folder 2432)
    - Berelson, Bernard Correspondence - Wayland, Sloan R., 1965-1973 (Box 262, Folder 2433)
    - Berelson, Bernard Correspondence - Westoff, Charles, 1965-1976 (Box 262, Folder 2434)
    - Berelson, Bernard Correspondence - Wilhelm, Harry, 1971-1975 (Box 262, Folder 2435)
    - Berelson, Bernard Correspondence - Wolfers, David (Box 262, Folder 2436)
    - Berelson, Bernard Correspondence - X-Y-Z (Box 262, Folder 2437)
    - Berelson, Bernard Files - U.N. - World Population Conference (WPC) - World Population Plan of Action, 1973-1974 (Box 263, Folder 2438)
    - Berelson, Bernard Files - Post-Bucharest (WPC) - Plan of Action, 1974 (Box 263, Folder 2439)
    - Berelson, Bernard Files - World Population Conference - Cultural, 1974 (Box 263, Folder 2440)
    - Berelson, Bernard Files - World Population Year - Tribune, 1974 (Box 263, Folder 2441)
    - Berelson, Bernard Files - World Population Year - Tribune, 1974 (Box 263, Folder 2442)
    - Berelson, Bernard Files - World Population Year - Tribune, 1973 (Box 263, Folder 2443)
    - Berelson, Bernard Files - World Population Year - Tribune - Members of Planning and Management Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 263, Folder 2444)
    - Berelson, Bernard Files - World Population Year - Carrillo-Flores, Townley, 1972-1974 (Box 263, Folder 2445)
    - Berelson, Bernard Files - World Population Year - Commission, 1972-1973 (Box 264, Folder 2446)
    - Berelson, Bernard Files - World Population Year - PC Lectureships, 1972-1973 (Box 264, Folder 2447)
    - Berelson, Bernard Files - World Population Year - Preliminary Documents, 1972 (Box 264, Folder 2448)
    - Berelson, Bernard Files - Princeton Advisory Council (Sociology Department), 1969-1973 (Box 264, Folder 2449)
    - Berelson, Bernard Files - Nobel Prize, 1970-1971 August (Box 264, Folder 2450)
    - Berelson, Bernard Files - Nobel Prize, 1971 September-1973 (Box 264, Folder 2451)
    - Berelson, Bernard Files - Nobel Prize - "Report on Progress", 1970 (Box 264, Folder 2452)
    - Berelson, Bernard Files - Nobel Prize - "The Nobel Peace Prize", 1970 (Box 264, Folder 2453)
    - Berelson, Bernard Files - Nobel Prize - Nobel Peace Prize 1972, 1971-1972 (Box 264, Folder 2454)
    - Berelson, Bernard Files - Nobel Prize - Norwegian Project, 1971-1972 (Box 264, Folder 2455)
    - Berelson, Bernard Files - Carnegie Corporation - Columbia Oral History Project, 1967-1970 (Box 265, Folder 2456)
    - Berelson, Bernard Files - Ford Foundation Oral History Project (Box 265, Folder 2457)
    - Berelson, Bernard Files - American Academy of Arts and Sciences (AAAS), 1972-1976 (Box 265, Folder 2458)
    - Berelson, Bernard Files - American Academy of Arts and Sciences (AAAS), 1970-1971 (Box 265, Folder 2459)
    - Berelson, Bernard Files - Alan Guttmacher Institute, 1976 (Box 265, Folder 2460)
    - Berelson, Bernard Files - Alan Guttmacher Institute, 1975 (Box 265, Folder 2461)
    - Berelson, Bernard Files - Alan Guttmacher Institute, 1974 (Box 266, Folder 2462)
    - Berelson, Bernard Files - Council on Foreign Relations - Meetings, 1974-1975 (Box 266, Folder 2463)
    - Berelson, Bernard Files - Council on Foreign Relations, 1973-1976 (Box 266, Folder 2464)
    - Berelson, Bernard Files - National Book Committee, 1964-1974 (Box 266, Folder 2465)
    - Berelson, Bernard Files - Hopper-Tabak-Berelson discussions (Meeting 1974 June 19) (Box 266, Folder 2466)
    - Berelson, Bernard Files - A.I.D., 1971 (Box 266, Folder 2467)
      Donor Agencies, Brochures, Proposals, Policy Papers
    - Berelson, Bernard Files - Ford Foundation, 1968-1973 (Box 266, Folder 2468)
    - Berelson, Bernard Files - Ford Foundation, 1967-1972; undated (Box 267, Folder 2469)
    - Berelson, Bernard Files - Ford Foundation, 1950-1961 (Box 267, Folder 2470)
    - Berelson, Bernard Files - Ford Foundation - India - Reports, Studies, 1969-1970 (Box 267, Folder 2471)
    - Berelson, Bernard Files - Ford Foundation - India - Reports, Studies, 1969 (Box 267, Folder 2472)
    - Berelson, Bernard Files - Ford Foundation - India - Reports, Studies, 1969 (Box 268, Folder 2473)
    - Berelson, Bernard Files - Ford Foundation - India - Reports, Studies, 1968. undated (Box 268, Folder 2474)
    - Berelson, Bernard Files - Ford Foundation - India - Reports, Studies, 1950; 1962 (Box 268, Folder 2475)
    - Berelson, Bernard Files - OECD, 1970-1975 (Box 268, Folder 2476)
    - Berelson, Bernard Files - OECD, 1969 (Box 268, Folder 2477)
    - Berelson, Bernard Files - OECD, 1968 (Box 269, Folder 2478)
    - Berelson, Bernard Files - Planned Parenthood-World Population (PP-WP), 1970-1973 (Box 269, Folder 2479)
    - Berelson, Bernard Files - Planned Parenthood-World Population (PP-WP), 1967-1969 (Box 269, Folder 2480)
    - Berelson, Bernard Files - United Nations, 1970-1973 (Box 269, Folder 2481)
    - Berelson, Bernard Files - United Nations, 1968-1969; undated (Box 269, Folder 2482)
    - Berelson, Bernard Files - United Nations Fund for Population Activities (UNFPA), 1972 (Box 269, Folder 2483)
    - Berelson, Bernard Files - United Nations Fund for Population Activities (UNFPA), 1969-1972 (Box 270, Folder 2484)
    - Berelson, Bernard Files - US Agency for International Development (AID), 1970-1973 (Box 270, Folder 2485)
    - Berelson, Bernard Files - US AID, 1968-1969 (Box 270, Folder 2486)
    - Berelson, Bernard Files - US AID, 1967-1968 (Box 270, Folder 2487)
    - Berelson, Bernard Files - World Health Organization (WHO), 1971-1973 (Box 270, Folder 2488)
    - Berelson, Bernard Files - World Health Organization (WHO), 1968-1970 (Box 271, Folder 2489)
    - Berelson, Bernard Files - World Health Organization (WHO), 1954-1966 (Box 271, Folder 2490)
    - Berelson, Bernard Files - World Bank, 1970-1975 (Box 271, Folder 2491)
    - Berelson, Bernard Files - World Bank, 1966-1969 (Box 271, Folder 2492)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Interdisciplinary Communications Prog. Conf., Elkridge, Maryland, 1970 November 8-11 (Box 271, Folder 2493)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Seminar on the Analysis of Security Prices, Chicago, 1970 November 5 (Box 271, Folder 2494)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Conference on Political Science and Population (at Population Council), 1970 October 29-30 (Box 271, Folder 2495)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Cornell University Undergraduate Conference on Population, 1970 October 15 (Box 271, Folder 2496)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Maternity and Child Health/Family Planning (MCH/FP) Meeting, 1970 September 21-23 (Box 271, Folder 2497)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Maternity and Child Health/Family Planning (MCH/FP) Meeting, 1970 September 21-23; 2015:FA432:001; Still image. 6 prints. (Box 11A)
      Still images have been separated from the file and assigned a unique separation number, as noted. Requests to access open special formats should reference the unique separation number.
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Southampton College, 1970 August 3-7 (Box 272, Folder 2498)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - WHO/Postpartum Meeting - Geneva, 1970 July 7-9 (Box 272, Folder 2499)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Cal Tech - Conference - Pasadena, CA, 1970 May 6; 7; 8 (Box 272, Folder 2500)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Population Association of America (PAA) Meeting, Atlanta, GA, 1970 April 16-18 (Box 272, Folder 2501)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Six World Congress - Obgyns. New York City, 1970 April 15 (Box 272, Folder 2502)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Rockefeller Foundation - Serbelloni Meeting, 1970 April 6-8 (Box 272, Folder 2503)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Population Policy Conference (at PC), 1970 March 6-7 (Box 272, Folder 2504)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - NIH Center for Population Research Conference - Washington D.C., 1970 Feb. 12-13 (Box 272, Folder 2505)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - North Africa Meeting (Ford/PC), 1970 Jan. 16-24 (Box 272, Folder 2506)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Miscellaneous Meetings, 1969 (Box 272, Folder 2507)
    - Senior Seminar in Foreign Policy - Amb. Jones, Bernard Berelson, Capt. Corley, 1969 January 22; 2015:FA432:002; Still image, 1 print. (Box 11A)
      Foreign Service Institute photo.
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS) - 1969 Annual Meeting, 1969 December 29 (Box 273, Folder 2508)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - OECD Meeting, Paris, 1969 November 18-20 (Box 273, Folder 2509)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - HEW Meeting (Corfman) Washington, D.C., 1969 September 19 (Box 273, Folder 2510)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Corfman -- Contraceptive Meeting, 1969 August 11-12 (Box 273, Folder 2511)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - WHO - Meeting of Advisors (Geneva), 1969 May 6-7 (Box 273, Folder 2512)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Government of Pakistan, Seminar on Family Planning, Dacca, 1969 January 28-February 4 (Box 273, Folder 2513)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Miscellaneous Meetings, 1968 (Box 273, Folder 2514)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - OECD/DAC Conference - Paris, France, 1968 December 2-5 (Box 273, Folder 2515)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - NAS Meeting, Washington, D.C., 1968 November 29-30 (Box 274, Folder 2516)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Abortion Conference, Hot Springs, VA, 1968 November 17-20 (Box 274, Folder 2517)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - World Bank, Washington, D.C., 1968 November 8 (Box 274, Folder 2518)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Taiwan Conference, 1968 May 1-7 (Box 274, Folder 2519)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Villa Bellagio, 1968 April 11-16 (Box 274, Folder 2520)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Ford Foundation - Population Conference, Rome, 1968 April 8-11 (Box 274, Folder 2521)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - WHO, Geneva, 1968 March 25 (Box 274, Folder 2522)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - South East Asia Development Advisory Group (SEADAG), New York, 1968 March 15-16 (Box 274, Folder 2523)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Demerath, New York (Prof. N. J. Demerath), 1968 March 7; 8 (Box 275, Folder 2524)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - National Academy of Science (NAS) Meeting, Washington, D.C., 1968 February 2 (Box 275, Folder 2525)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Meeting on Population and Economic Development, New York City, 1968 January 25 (Box 275, Folder 2526)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Council for the Advancement of Science Writing (CASW), New Jersey, 1968 January 24 (Box 275, Folder 2527)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - World Bank, Washington, D.C., 1968 January 23 (Box 275, Folder 2528)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Miscellaneous Meetings, 1963-1967 (Box 275, Folder 2529)
    - Senior Seminar in Foreign Policy - Amb. Jones, Bernard Berelson, Mr. Eliasson, 1967 November 9; 2015:FA432:003; Still image, 1 print. (Box 11A)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Miscellaneous Meetings, 1964-1965 (Box 275, Folder 2530)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Association of American Medical Colleges (AAMC), 1967 October 29 (Box 275, Folder 2531)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - National Association of Manufacturers (NAM), New York, 1967 October 4 (Box 275, Folder 2532)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Postpartum Meeting, 1967 September 11-13 (Box 275, Folder 2533)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - UNESCO, Paris, 1967 July 6-12 (Box 276, Folder 2534)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Family Planning/Urban Poor/Medical Schools (University Club, NYC), 1967 June 28 (Box 276, Folder 2535)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Behavioral Sciences Conference, Washington, D.C. (Corfman), 1969 June 7-9 (Box 276, Folder 2536)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Council on Foundations, Boston, 1967 May 10-12 (Box 276, Folder 2537)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Bowdoin College, Maine, 1967 April 21-22 (Box 276, Folder 2538)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Invasion of Privacy Symposium, 1966 October 28 (Box 276, Folder 2539)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - American Council on Education, New Orleans, 1966 October 12-14 (Box 276, Folder 2540)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Population Council Retreat, New York City, 1966 June 8 (Box 276, Folder 2541)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Summit II, New York City, 1966 April 15 (Box 276, Folder 2542)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Postpartum (PC Conference), New York City, 1966 January 20-21 (Box 276, Folder 2543)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Summit I (PC Conference), New York City, 1966 January 7 (Box 277, Folder 2544)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Measurement and Evaluation (PC Seminar), New York City, 1965 December 3-4 (Box 277, Folder 2545)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Population Council Retreat, New York City, 1966 June 8 (Box 277, Folder 2546)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - World Population Conference (UN) Belgrade, 1965 August 30-September 10 (Box 277, Folder 2547)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - International Conference on Family Planning Programs, Geneva, 1965 August 23-27 (Box 277, Folder 2548)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Second IUD Conference (PC Meeting), New York City, 1964 October 2-3 (Box 277, Folder 2549)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Population Association of America Meeting, San Francisco, 1964 June11-13 (Box 277, Folder 2550)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Population Symposium, American Association of Public Opinion Research - World Association of Public Opinion Research, 1964 May 5 (Box 277, Folder 2551)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - National Conference on Higher Education, Chicago, 1964 April 19-22 (Box 277, Folder 2552)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Population Council Strategy and Tactics Meeting, New York City, 1964 January 24-25 (Box 277, Folder 2553)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Population Conference, Rockefeller Foundation, 1963 June 18-19 (Box 277, Folder 2554)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Media Workshop, University of California, Berkeley, 1963 January 14 (Box 277, Folder 2555)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Reports on Trips, 1968-1973 (Box 278, Folder 2556)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Reports on Trips, 1962-1965 (Box 278, Folder 2557)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Declinations, 1974 (Box 278, Folder 2558)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Ford Foundation Conference on Social Science Research: Population and Development, NYC, 1974 October 29-30 (Box 278, Folder 2559)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Ford Foundation Meeting, Cali, Colombia, 1974 October 14-17 (Box 278, Folder 2560)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - ICCR Meeting, Abby Aldrich, 1974 October 9-11 (Box 278, Folder 2561)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - ICCR Meeting, Abby Aldrich, 1974 October 9-11 (Box 278, Folder 2562)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - World Population Year Conference - Bucharest, 1974 August 19-30 (Box 278, Folder 2563)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - International Committee on the Management of Population Programs (ICOMP), Annual Conference, Glen Cove, NY, 1974 July 29-31 (Box 279, Folder 2564)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Instituto Nacional de la Nutricion Conference, Mexico, 1974 June 21 (Box 279, Folder 2565)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Planned Parenthood-World Population (PP-WP) - International Convocation, Hotel Americana, NYC, 1974 June 20 (Box 279, Folder 2566)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Satellite Data Workshop, NYC (at PC), 1974 May 10 (Box 279, Folder 2567)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Princeton Lectureship, 1972-1974 (Box 279, Folder 2568)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Declinations, 1973 (Box 279, Folder 2569)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - American Immigration and Citizenship Conference, New York, 1973 November 2 (Box 279, Folder 2570)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - International Planned Parenthood Federation - Planning for the Future - Hotel Metropole, 1973 October 22-27 (Box 279, Folder 2571)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Planned Parenthood of Westchester (NY) - Population Commission talk, 1973 May 17 (Box 280, Folder 2572)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Bellagio III, Conference, Italy, 1973 May 10-12 (Box 280, Folder 2573)
    - Bellagio III, Population Conference, 1973 May 10-12; Still image, 1 print. (Box 11A)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Population Association of America (PAA) - Annual Meeting, New Orleans, LA, 1973 April 26-28 (Box 280, Folder 2574)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Meeting on Population at International Affairs (at Council on Foreign Relations), 1974 April 17 (Box 280, Folder 2575)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Taylor/Berelson Program - Advisory Committee Meeting, New York, 1973 March 28-30 (Box 280, Folder 2576)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Oxford Workshop, 1973 March 15-18 (Box 280, Folder 2577)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Population Review Committee, Harvard, 1973 February 8-9 (Box 280, Folder 2578)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Field Staff Meeting, Tarrytown, NY, 1972 December 11-15 (Box 280, Folder 2579)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Field Staff Meeting, Tarrytown, NY, 1972 December 11-15 (Box 281, Folder 2580)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - State Population Conference, Amherst, MA, 1972 November 29-30 (Box 281, Folder 2581)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - PC-WHO Meeting, New York City, 1972 October 20-22 (Box 281, Folder 2582)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Mexico (Meeting with Zubiran), 1973 October 19-20 (Box 281, Folder 2583)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Symposium: Population Policy in Developed Countries, Belgrade, 1972 October 4-7 (Box 281, Folder 2584)
    - Symposium: Population Policy in Developed Countries, Belgrade, 1972 October 4-7; 2015:FA432:005; Still image, 10 prints. (Box 11A)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Harvard Inter-faculty Seminar, Boston, 1972 September 19 (Box 281, Folder 2585)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Ortho Pharmaceutical Corporation Conference, Poconos (Westoff), 1972 September 6-7 (Box 281, Folder 2586)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - United Nations Population Commission Meeting, New York, 1972 August 7-15 (Box 281, Folder 2587)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - North Africa Regional Grant - Freedman et al., June 26-27 meeting, 1972 (Box 281, Folder 2588)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Declinations, 1972 (Box 282, Folder 2589)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Miscellaneous Meetings, 1972 (Box 282, Folder 2590)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - National Bureau of Economic Research/PC Conference (Economics), Harrison House, Long Island, NY, 1972 June 8-9 (Box 282, Folder 2591)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Resources for the Future/PC Conference, Washington, D.C., 1972 May 10-11 (Box 282, Folder 2592)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - Lab. of Human Reproduction and Reproductive Biology, Harvard, 1972 May 8 (Box 282, Folder 2593)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - American Association of Planned Parenthood Physicians (AAPPP), Detroit, 1972 April 7 (Box 282, Folder 2594)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Meetings and Conferences - East Aftica Trip, 1972 January 12-28 (Box 282, Folder 2595)
    - East Africa Trip, Bernard Berelson, Dr. Mahmud Fawzy, Dr. Esmat Abdel Meguid, 1972 January 15; 2015:FA432:006; Still image, 2 prints. (Box 11A)